### ABOUT ME

Incoming graduate student with 2+ years of experience in all stages of the lifecycle to deliver projects on the time and on budget. Seeking greater responsibility as a project manager for motive, where my experience will drive client-facing project.

# WEBSITES & SOCIAL LINKS



nisseemmagar.com.np

# EXTRA CURRICULAR ACTIVITIES

- PTE Instructor (Part time)
- Member of Nepal Open Source Klub - NCIT and organized different tech events like hackathon and IT meetups.
- Volunteered during COVID-19
   Pandemic [ Institute for Nepal and Hamro Sano Prayas ]
- Participated in Intra-College Software Expo.

### **KEY SKILLS**

### PROJECT MANAGEMENT

- Agile Methodology
- Risk Management
- Effective Communication
- Documentation
- Leadership

### DEVELOPMENT

- React JS
- · Version Control (GIT)
- HTML & CSS
- · Responsive Designs
- Figma and Adobe Illustrator
- · Database Management

#### **HOBBIES**

- 🉎 Yoga
- Reading and Collecting Books
- Social Media Content Creation
- 🚇 Public Speaking

# NISSEEM RANA MAGAR

ASSOCIATE PROJECT MANAGER

# **EDUCATION**

Bachelor Of Computer Engineering [ 2015 - 2019 | Completed ] Nepal College Of Information Technology Final Year Project:

Construction and Implementation of Neural Network Library
Created own NN library and implement it to build web interface for disease prediction
system, and to recognize handwritten digits

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

### ConvergeTree Technologies Pvt Ltd - Associate Project Manager

April 2022 - Present

- Delivered a B2B software product for enterprises to get real-time credit monitoring alerts.
- · Worked with C-level suite to create vision and goals for project.
- Implemented and organized daily stand up meetings, sprint planning, retrospective meetings, learning sessions with the management and development team.
- Collaborated in different software projects like payment system, Digital wallet system,
   CRM's, ERP and many more to work cross functionally with software which enabled me to understand different business logic.
- Met 100% of deadlines and project goals, earning a credibility upon completing different outsourced projects.
- Assisted Project Manager to make a client production schedule, so that they would know when they could expect to give feedback, review and approve the projects.

#### Teksewa Services Pvt Ltd - Associate Project Manager (Internship)

December 2021 - March 2022

- Participated in over viewing backlog prioritization, sprint planning, daily stand ups, change management and overall execution.
- Prepared necessary documents for various stages of project in consultation with senior project manager.
- · Reported to senior management on project status.

#### ConvergeTree Technologies Pvt Ltd - Frontend Developer

September 2020 – November 2021

- Involved in different software development process to develop in house and out sourced project.
- Consulted to GSD cloud services using the MERN technology to provide cloud services.
- Provided expert solutions for customizing Shopify theme designs per client needs.
- Used Figma and Adobe illustrator for better User Experience.

# Informatha Technologies - Software Developer (Internship)

January 2020 – March 2020

- Used html5, css3 and JavaScript to build UI pages for the inhouse News Portal
   System
- Worked on improving the programming skills and developing the professional culture.